Hello everyone, this video is for you to introduce the new function of KOLO2025.1
First is the main function part
Use our 3D pen virtual model tool
Directly draw on the model
Even if you don't know how to do it, you can freely play your creative in KOLO
Let you create a three-dimensional costume
This update upgraded the tool
Not only is it drawn on the virtual model
Just use the shortcut key
You can start to leave the virtual model surface
Draw in any position in the 3D space
All other common shortcuts are still usable
In addition, there are some new functions
For example, add a circle around the virtual model
And show the distance from the point of your drawing to the virtual model
Just like this, you can quickly draw a costume in KOLO
Use the flat flat panel tool to convert these lines into paper
The system will automatically arrange and sew the panel for you
Finally, add the fabric
One piece of clothing is completed
In order to make the performance of the water wash of牛仔 more relaxed and intuitive
We have added a material type of single-seam cloth
And provided eight types of water-washing pre-set
For water washing
Drying washing
Speed washing
Slipper washing
Acid washing
Sterilizing
Smell Yang washing
And custom-assigned
For you to adjust and test in KOLO
Each water-washing model will provide different slide options according to the water-washing method chosen
Each water-washing model will have a cycle time option and a phonical module option
As the time is longer, the color will be lighter
All water-washing options can be set to the same setting
For example, if there are two types of water-washing, you can choose one type of water washing, one type of water-washing, and another type of water-washing.
The longer the time, the lighter the color, the more likely the water-washing.
All water-washing options can be selected for each type of water-washing.
If you want to use your own water wash effect picture, the custom option is very suitable for you.
You can add your own water wash picture here and use the slider to adjust the details.
It only takes a few minutes to create a custom B-pattern water wash visual effect.
The picture shows you the effect of eight water wash types.
Now you can implement the no-need cutting and sewing version.
You can apply different textures and colors to the version.
This function is designed to help all real designers.
Let you design and make seamless clothing in CLO.
CLO provides a variety of work processes to create these new seamless division lines.
It provides unlimited possibilities for the creation of seamless clothing.
You can use the hook and loop tool to hook the inner line or the basic line into a seamless division line.
Then apply different fabrics to the area after the division.
You only need to apply different fabrics to the area after the division.
Just like how you applied the fabric to the version before, you can easily apply the fabric to the area after the division.
You can also use the seamless division line tool in the edited version to create the original line.
After applying different fabrics, you can see the difference after simulation.
Finally, the seamless division tool itself allows you to create a seamless division line on the version.
Then you can apply the fabric to the version after applying the material window.
You can also use the edit or edit version tool to adjust the line you created.
And you can use the edit texture tool to adjust the texture of each seamless division.
This way you can easily make a more interesting outfit without cutting any version.
Now you can simulate the software model.
Apply the OBJ file to the OBJ file.
You can try to use it to simulate pillow or sponge.
You can see that when you open the software model simulation, the shape of the virtual model will change according to the difference in the fabric.
This improvement can also be applied to clothes and accessories such as shoulder pads.
After inserting them as OBJ files, adjust the layer between shoulder pads and clothes first.
Then turn on the simulation.
Now I will apply the software model simulation effect for it.
I can control its rigidity by using the slider.
This effect is similar to the sponge.
This improves the real feeling of clothing created in the shell.
We updated the seamless division tool to show the selection and optimize the seamless division display effect.
So that it can be better applied to the process unit.
In the seamless attribute editor,
you can choose the ratio of the virtual model.
And you can edit its details.
Including length, length, width, thickness, width and thickness between the lines.
This makes it easier to check the lines in the model simulation.
We have further updated the library.
Now when you open it, you will see an independent CONNECT label.
In this label, you can check all the purchase records and all the high-quality resources on the website.
Use the selection option.
You can select all the resources in CONNECT.
And narrow the search range to find the content you need.
We have improved the layout of the CLOSE SET in the new library.
Make it consistent with the layout of the web page.
Make it easier for you to navigate and search for projects.
Now all the AI functions are available in the AI button next to the library.
It is convenient to visit our AI functions.
The process and steps of using these AI functions are the same as before.
Here I will use the AI rendering amplifier as an example.
As before,
I can upload the rendering image to my work area.
By entering a prompt or automatically generating a random prompt.
To generate different AI faces.
After selecting the face, you can preview the face.
You can even use our updated optimization options to continue to optimize the image.
To get a more realistic synthesis effect.
The last background options in the version can also be found here.
I can import the image and preview.
You can also let CLOSE generate the background and preview these options.
After you are satisfied with the result, you can save the image.
From 2020 to 2021, you can save the image.
Now I have a new project.
This project will be uploaded to my work area.
From the 2025.1 version, all AI functions will be defaulted.
If you want to use AI, you need to activate it manually.
You can activate AI Studio by clicking on the plugin in the main menu bar.
Jump to the official website page, log in to the account and activate it.
Now you can save the selected version and component as one costume.
This makes it easier to extract all parts of the project file.
And add it to other project files.
For example, I want to save this bag.
Then add it to my other project file.
With this function, I can easily create a complete set of costumes.
We added a zipper option card to the object window.
You can save the zipper as an overall quick and easy application and edit it.
You can still edit and adjust the zipper separately.
We integrated the fabric generator and the seamless fabric generator into CloFab.
You can enter CloFab under the fabric window and the fabric under the main menu bar.
It can also be linked to our new CloZFab fabric measurement kit.
In CloFab, you can create fabric information at the top.
Then enter the fabric attribute part and import your PBR sticker.
Use the same process as the previous seamless fabric generator.
Create a seamless cycle by automatic or manual operation.
After getting a satisfactory cycle, you can enter the physical attribute part.
Follow the same process as the fabric generator.
Select the type and ingredients of the fabric.
Enter the specific percentage and weight of the ingredients.
And check the change of the spiral.
After you are satisfied with the physical and physical effects of the fabric.
You can save it as a document.
Once you click this posted Fen and as a document.
Clulab displays Clulab- poststar and Clulab- purchase document for you.
Then you can import it into the body window and apply it to your outfit.
Now when you add a project or outfit.
You can select a color to be added.
If the number of flags is less than the current file, Kolo will directly apply the first flag to the rest of the flags.
You can add and adjust other flags.
It's never that easy to put a code in Kolo.
Now you can choose which points you need to put a code in Kolo and which points you don't need to put a code in Kolo.
On the right-click on the selected point, you can choose to convert it to a non-code point or a code point.
If the point becomes a non-code point, it will follow the code rules that are closest to the code point.
This is also applicable to the curve point.
We hope this will make it easier for Kolo users to put codes.
In the 2025.1 version, we have further updated the quick photo option.
We have added the function of self-defined line shapes and colors to make it easier for everyone to edit different types of lines.
This optimization is for outputting quick photo files.
We hope to improve the usability of quick photo files, so that they are not only limited to printing, but can also be applied to cutters, which makes it more convenient for Kolo to connect and produce.
Now you can export and import standard DXF files in Kolo.
In the DXF export or import and export window, a DXF option will appear in the download menu.
It is used for standard DXF files, which enhances the compatibility with other CAD software.
Our version of the generator tool expands the AI function.
Now you can read any image, not just the style image.
You can upload your favorite clothing image.
Then the version generator will generate the version according to the image.
Of course, you can continue to edit according to the size.
After you are satisfied, you can choose to create.
Then the clothing will automatically arrange and store it on the virtual model.
All you need to do is simulate and check the wearing effect.
We have added a new feature to the editing version.
Now it is able to align with the axis of the page.
This way, you don't need to process the repetition.
We have added the editing option to the previewer in the new version.
The attribute editor now provides more down racial options for the pick position.
The cutout at the corner of the cutout is more accurately positioned on the seam.
We have also updated the cutout settings in the user's custom definition.
This will help all users in the unified company to view the cutout.
We hope that these improvements will improve the usability of the software,
and will be more accurate when connecting to production in the future.
There are more functions in the Kolo 2025.1 version.
Please check our official website and follow our new features introduction video.
Thank you very much for watching.
I hope you like the update in the new version,
and enjoy using these functions.
I hope you have fun playing in Kolo.